<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Open World on</title><link>https://rslifka.github.io/sliflist/docs/world/</link><description>Recent content in Open World on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><atom:link href="https://rslifka.github.io/sliflist/docs/world/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Black Scorpion-4sr</title><link>https://rslifka.github.io/sliflist/docs/world/black_scorpion_4sr/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://rslifka.github.io/sliflist/docs/world/black_scorpion_4sr/</guid><description>No general overview as only PvP rolls featured for this one!
💪 Mercules Collector&amp;rsquo;s Edition (Feat. Rampage) (pvp) Let&amp;rsquo;s call this the &amp;ldquo;Mercules&amp;rdquo; roll, since listening to the podcast linked above informed its creation. All Stability, all day, with better Aim Assistance and mobility from Moving Target.
Collector&amp;rsquo;s Edition Perks
Barrels: Chambered Compensator Magazines: Steady Rounds Perks 1: Moving Target, Zen Moment Perks 2: Rampage Masterworks: Stability MW Extended Perks (referred to with a &amp;lsquo;+&amp;rsquo; below)</description></item><item><title>BrayTech Werewolf</title><link>https://rslifka.github.io/sliflist/docs/world/braytech_werewolf/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://rslifka.github.io/sliflist/docs/world/braytech_werewolf/</guid><description>The BrayTech Werewolf is a 450 RPM &amp;ldquo;Precision Frame&amp;rdquo; Kinetic Auto Rifle first introduced in Season 8. It&amp;rsquo;s now available in the 2020 Festival of the Lost event, with random rolls. The only competitive AR archetype right now are the 600s, so you&amp;rsquo;re gambling on an eventual sandbox change for this to be more effective in PvP.
🐺 Werewolves not Swearwolves (pvp) With completely vertical recoil and loads of Stability, this will be an absolutely shredder should 450s get a buff.</description></item><item><title>Cold Front</title><link>https://rslifka.github.io/sliflist/docs/world/cold_front/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://rslifka.github.io/sliflist/docs/world/cold_front/</guid><description>Cold Front is a 750 RPM Aggressive Frame (&amp;ldquo;High damage, high recoil&amp;rdquo;) Kinetic Submachine Gun, first introduced long ago during the Season 9 Dawning event. It&amp;rsquo;s back once again with a whole new set of perks from Year 4. If you want to see the old perks, here&amp;rsquo;s a still from Aztec&amp;rsquo;s review in 2019.
🥶 Endless Winter (pvp,pve) Surplus + One for All + all the Stability you can get.</description></item><item><title>Compass Rose</title><link>https://rslifka.github.io/sliflist/docs/world/compass_rose/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://rslifka.github.io/sliflist/docs/world/compass_rose/</guid><description>Compass Rose is a Precision Frame, Solar shotgun. It was available only during the Season 14 Solstice event.
🧲 Magnetic North (pvp) Classic &amp;ldquo;SnapDraw&amp;rdquo; shotgun roll. Compass Rose can roll with a few Range- increasing barrels in addition to just Full Choke and Rifled, so our odds of picking up these rolls is a bit better.
Collector&amp;rsquo;s Edition Perks
Barrels: Rifled Barrel, Full Choke Magazines: Accurized Rounds Perks 1: Quickdraw Perks 2: Snapshot Masterworks: Range MW Extended Perks (referred to with a &amp;lsquo;+&amp;rsquo; below)</description></item><item><title>Dire Promise</title><link>https://rslifka.github.io/sliflist/docs/world/dire_promise/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://rslifka.github.io/sliflist/docs/world/dire_promise/</guid><description>The Dire Promise is a 140 RPM Hand Cannon that was re-issued all the way back in Season 10 and much has changed. Sunsetting was introduced and then rolled back, 150 RPM HCs were collapsed into the 140 RPM frames and 110 RPMs were upgraded to 120 RPM, turning them into absolute PvP monsters. 140s are middle- of-the-pack but still pack a decent punch.
🙏 Promises Made and Kept (pvp) 140s crave Stability.</description></item><item><title>Eternity's Edge</title><link>https://rslifka.github.io/sliflist/docs/world/eternitys_edge/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://rslifka.github.io/sliflist/docs/world/eternitys_edge/</guid><description>Eternity&amp;rsquo;s Edge is a Solar sword that was reissued as a Vortex Frame in Season 14.
⏳ Forever and a Day (pve) With Surrounded and Relentless you&amp;rsquo;ll be slicing for what seems like forever. C/o this analysis, Jagged Edge is the clear choice for the first column, but you&amp;rsquo;ll want to make sure your reserves are increased in armor. Infinite Guard is locked on this weapon, so you&amp;rsquo;re stuck with it :)</description></item><item><title>Hawkmoon</title><link>https://rslifka.github.io/sliflist/docs/world/hawkmoon/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://rslifka.github.io/sliflist/docs/world/hawkmoon/</guid><description>Hawkmoon is a 140 RPM Exotic Hand Cannon, re-issued from Destiny 1 featuring random rolls! The base stats are terrific and it&amp;rsquo;s hard to argue that any single roll is &amp;ldquo;bad&amp;rdquo; per se, but there are certainly some rolls that are more desireable than others from a min/max&amp;rsquo;ers perspective.
If you haven&amp;rsquo;t already, complete the catalyst! Completing it grants you the masterwork:
&amp;ldquo;Increased magazine size. Grants increased handling, reload and weapon range based on the number of stacks of Paracausal Charge.</description></item><item><title>Honor's Edge</title><link>https://rslifka.github.io/sliflist/docs/world/honors_edge/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://rslifka.github.io/sliflist/docs/world/honors_edge/</guid><description>Honor&amp;rsquo;s Edge (HE) is available in the World Drops loot pool in Season 11, originally being re-issued back in Season 10. The main difference between HE and SS14 is that HE can roll with Surrounded and Flash Counter, two both amazing perks.
Surrounded + Surrounded Spec ends up giving you a massive 35% damage increase and since a Sword is in-your-face there&amp;rsquo;s a high chance you&amp;rsquo;ll proc this regularly. Flash Counter not only disorients but applies a 20% debuff!</description></item><item><title>Hung Jury (Adept)</title><link>https://rslifka.github.io/sliflist/docs/world/hung_jury_adept/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://rslifka.github.io/sliflist/docs/world/hung_jury_adept/</guid><description>The Adept Hung Jury is available from Grandmaster Nightfalls. It&amp;rsquo;s the same as the Hung Jury, with the exception that it can take Adept mods and gains +2 to all attributes when Masterworked.
🛡 TrueVanguard&amp;rsquo;s Choice - The Three-Tapper (pvp) With Box Breathing you can three-tap!
Collector&amp;rsquo;s Edition Perks
Barrels: Polygonal Rifling Magazines: Steady Rounds Perks 1: Moving Target, Rapid Hit, Heating Up Perks 2: Box Breathing Masterworks: Stability MW Extended Perks (referred to with a &amp;lsquo;+&amp;rsquo; below)</description></item><item><title>Seventh Seraph Carbine</title><link>https://rslifka.github.io/sliflist/docs/world/seventh_seraph_carbine/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://rslifka.github.io/sliflist/docs/world/seventh_seraph_carbine/</guid><description>The Seventh Seraph Carbine (SSC) is a 450 RPM &amp;ldquo;Precision Frame&amp;rdquo; Kinetic Auto Rifle. Let&amp;rsquo;s start with a quick comparison to randomly-rolled 450s, over on light.gg. In general the 450s are fairly the same stat-wise, with a material deviation in Aim Assist for the SSC; easily addressable with an Aim Assist mod.
🐴 Cavalry (pvp) Slideshot paired with either Moving Target or Rangefinder is buffing so much of what this Auto Rifle needs help with: Stability and AA.</description></item></channel></rss>