<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Open World on</title><link>https://rslifka.github.io/sliflist/docs/world/</link><description>Recent content in Open World on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><atom:link href="https://rslifka.github.io/sliflist/docs/world/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Black Scorpion-4sr</title><link>https://rslifka.github.io/sliflist/docs/world/black_scorpion_4sr/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://rslifka.github.io/sliflist/docs/world/black_scorpion_4sr/</guid><description>No general overview as only PvP rolls featured for this one!
💪 Mercules Collector&amp;rsquo;s Edition (Feat. Rampage) (pvp) Let&amp;rsquo;s call this the &amp;ldquo;Mercules&amp;rdquo; roll, since listening to the podcast linked above informed its creation. All Stability, all day, with better Aim Assistance and mobility from Moving Target.
Collector&amp;rsquo;s Edition Perks
Barrels: Chambered Compensator Magazines: Steady Rounds Perks 1: Moving Target, Zen Moment Perks 2: Rampage Masterworks: Stability MW Extended Perks (referred to with a &amp;lsquo;+&amp;rsquo; below)</description></item><item><title>BrayTech Werewolf</title><link>https://rslifka.github.io/sliflist/docs/world/braytech_werewolf/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://rslifka.github.io/sliflist/docs/world/braytech_werewolf/</guid><description>The BrayTech Werewolf is a 450 RPM &amp;ldquo;Precision Frame&amp;rdquo; Kinetic Auto Rifle first introduced in Season 8. It&amp;rsquo;s now available in the 2020 Festival of the Lost event, with random rolls. The only competitive AR archetype right now are the 600s, so you&amp;rsquo;re gambling on an eventual sandbox change for this to be more effective in PvP.
🐺 Werewolves not Swearwolves (pvp) With completely vertical recoil and loads of Stability, this will be an absolutely shredder should 450s get a buff.</description></item><item><title>Cold Front</title><link>https://rslifka.github.io/sliflist/docs/world/cold_front/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://rslifka.github.io/sliflist/docs/world/cold_front/</guid><description>Cold Front is a 750 RPM Aggressive Frame (&amp;ldquo;High damage, high recoil&amp;rdquo;) Kinetic Submachine Gun, first introduced long ago during the Season 9 Dawning event. It&amp;rsquo;s back once again with a whole new set of perks from Year 4. If you want to see the old perks, here&amp;rsquo;s a still from Aztec&amp;rsquo;s review in 2019.
🥶 Endless Winter (pvp,pve) Surplus + One for All + all the Stability you can get.</description></item><item><title>Compass Rose</title><link>https://rslifka.github.io/sliflist/docs/world/compass_rose/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://rslifka.github.io/sliflist/docs/world/compass_rose/</guid><description>Compass Rose is a Precision Frame, Solar shotgun. It was available only during the Season 14 Solstice event.
🧲 Magnetic North (pvp) Classic &amp;ldquo;SnapDraw&amp;rdquo; shotgun roll. Compass Rose can roll with a few Range- increasing barrels in addition to just Full Choke and Rifled, so our odds of picking up these rolls is a bit better.
Collector&amp;rsquo;s Edition Perks
Barrels: Rifled Barrel, Full Choke Magazines: Accurized Rounds Perks 1: Quickdraw Perks 2: Snapshot Masterworks: Range MW Extended Perks (referred to with a &amp;lsquo;+&amp;rsquo; below)</description></item><item><title>Dire Promise</title><link>https://rslifka.github.io/sliflist/docs/world/dire_promise/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://rslifka.github.io/sliflist/docs/world/dire_promise/</guid><description>The Dire Promise is a 140 RPM Hand Cannon that was re-issued all the way back in Season 10 and much has changed. Sunsetting was introduced and then rolled back, 150 RPM HCs were collapsed into the 140 RPM frames and 110 RPMs were upgraded to 120 RPM, turning them into absolute PvP monsters. 140s are middle- of-the-pack but still pack a decent punch.
🙏 Promises Made and Kept (pvp) 140s crave Stability.</description></item><item><title>Hung Jury (Adept)</title><link>https://rslifka.github.io/sliflist/docs/world/hung_jury_adept/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://rslifka.github.io/sliflist/docs/world/hung_jury_adept/</guid><description>The Adept Hung Jury is available from Grandmaster Nightfalls. It&amp;rsquo;s the same as the Hung Jury, with the exception that it can take Adept mods and gains +2 to all attributes when Masterworked.
🛡 TrueVanguard&amp;rsquo;s Choice - The Three-Tapper (pvp) With Box Breathing you can three-tap!
Collector&amp;rsquo;s Edition Perks
Barrels: Polygonal Rifling Magazines: Steady Rounds Perks 1: Moving Target, Rapid Hit, Heating Up Perks 2: Box Breathing Masterworks: Stability MW Extended Perks (referred to with a &amp;lsquo;+&amp;rsquo; below)</description></item><item><title>Seventh Seraph Carbine</title><link>https://rslifka.github.io/sliflist/docs/world/seventh_seraph_carbine/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://rslifka.github.io/sliflist/docs/world/seventh_seraph_carbine/</guid><description>The Seventh Seraph Carbine (SSC) is a 450 RPM &amp;ldquo;Precision Frame&amp;rdquo; Kinetic Auto Rifle. Let&amp;rsquo;s start with a quick comparison to randomly-rolled 450s, over on light.gg. In general the 450s are fairly the same stat-wise, with a material deviation in Aim Assist for the SSC; easily addressable with an Aim Assist mod.
🐴 Cavalry (pvp) Slideshot paired with either Moving Target or Rangefinder is buffing so much of what this Auto Rifle needs help with: Stability and AA.</description></item><item><title>Seventh Seraph CQC-12</title><link>https://rslifka.github.io/sliflist/docs/world/seventh_seraph_cqc_12/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://rslifka.github.io/sliflist/docs/world/seventh_seraph_cqc_12/</guid><description>The CQC-12 is an 80 RPM &amp;ldquo;Lightweight Frame&amp;rdquo; shotgun in the energy slot. Through leveling the season pass, you unlock a chance for it to drop at the conclusion of Gambit, Crucible and Strike activities. You can&amp;rsquo;t really &amp;ldquo;farm&amp;rdquo; it per se. The good news is that there&amp;rsquo;s only four perks in the final two columns meaning it&amp;rsquo;s not incredibly difficult to get the perks you might be interested in. See how it compares to other randomly-rolled 80 RPMs over on light.</description></item><item><title>Seventh Seraph Officer Revolver</title><link>https://rslifka.github.io/sliflist/docs/world/seventh_seraph_officer_revolver/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://rslifka.github.io/sliflist/docs/world/seventh_seraph_officer_revolver/</guid><description>The Officer Revolver is a 180 RPM Kinetic Hand Cannon. See how it compares to other 180 RPM Hand Cannons over on light.gg Let&amp;rsquo;s start off with Mercules and Kyt from the latest Massive Breakdown podcast. Turns out they aren&amp;rsquo;t super hot on the Officer&amp;rsquo;s Revolver.
🏔🌱 Drewsky&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Planted Range&amp;rdquo; (pvp) &amp;ldquo;Timed Payload?! That&amp;rsquo;s supposed to be positively horrible. Doesn&amp;rsquo;t it lower your TTK?&amp;quot; Well, it causes double the flinch and the explosion has no range falloff.</description></item><item><title>Seventh Seraph SAW</title><link>https://rslifka.github.io/sliflist/docs/world/seventh_seraph_saw/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://rslifka.github.io/sliflist/docs/world/seventh_seraph_saw/</guid><description>Drewsky has a great review of the Bane of Sorrow, another 360 RPM &amp;ldquo;High-Impact Frame&amp;rdquo; Machine Gun. From the review, it hits for 48 crit / 38 body (TTK 0.5s / 0.83s). It&amp;rsquo;s got terrific range and flinches like crazy.
🎯 Sniper MG (pvp) Any basic roll will chew up Guardians with a lot of flinch. Let&amp;rsquo;s add Range and Stability where we can, while seeing what Opening Shot can do.</description></item></channel></rss>