<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Open World on</title><link>https://rslifka.github.io/sliflist/docs/world/</link><description>Recent content in Open World on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><atom:link href="https://rslifka.github.io/sliflist/docs/world/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>[Berenger's Memory](https://www.light.gg/db/items/407621213)</title><link>https://rslifka.github.io/sliflist/docs/world/berengers_memory/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://rslifka.github.io/sliflist/docs/world/berengers_memory/</guid><description>Season 11 is the first time we&amp;rsquo;ve seen Berenger&amp;rsquo;s Memory since Destiny 2 Year 1 (i.e. Season 1). It&amp;rsquo;s the first time it&amp;rsquo;s been available with random rolls. It&amp;rsquo;s a Rapid-Fire Frame with an interesting perk layout that doesn&amp;rsquo;t ultimately result in a lot of super interesting rolls.
PvE Thoughts All of the best perks are in the final column. There are OK perks in the third column but nothing that super synergizes moreso than the other GLs that can roll in this slot.</description></item><item><title>[Black Scorpion-4sr](https://www.light.gg/db/items/525750263)</title><link>https://rslifka.github.io/sliflist/docs/world/black_scorpion_4sr/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://rslifka.github.io/sliflist/docs/world/black_scorpion_4sr/</guid><description>The Black Scorpion (now sunset) is Rapid-Fire Frame Scout Rifle in the Energy Slot. If you&amp;rsquo;re looking for a modern-day Rapid-Fire, check out the Trustee from Deep Stone Crypt.
PvP Thoughts CoolGuy&amp;rsquo;s review (8/2019) is great source of info for the Black Scorpion, as well as the Massive Breakdown Podcast Ep. 148. There are seven perks in the final two columns (versus the usual four to six) and during Season 9, this weapon does not benefit from the Rank 92 extra-final-column-perk bonus.</description></item><item><title>[BrayTech Werewolf](https://www.light.gg/db/items/528834068)</title><link>https://rslifka.github.io/sliflist/docs/world/braytech_werewolf/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://rslifka.github.io/sliflist/docs/world/braytech_werewolf/</guid><description>The BrayTech Werewolf is a 450 RPM &amp;ldquo;Precision Frame&amp;rdquo; Kinetic Auto Rifle first introduced in Season 8. It&amp;rsquo;s now available in the 2020 Festival of the Lost event, with random rolls. Obtaining this Auto Rifle is a pretty grim affair, behind three levels of RNG:
You need Cipher Decoders to drop, which they have a chance of doing do at the end of most activities (Ordeal, Strike playlist, Crucible, etc.</description></item><item><title>[Cold Front](https://www.light.gg/db/items/1506719573)</title><link>https://rslifka.github.io/sliflist/docs/world/cold_front/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://rslifka.github.io/sliflist/docs/world/cold_front/</guid><description>Cold Front is a 750 RPM Aggressive Frame (&amp;ldquo;High damage, high recoil&amp;rdquo;) Kinetic Submachine Gun, first introduced long ago during the Season 9 Dawning event. It&amp;rsquo;s back once again with a whole new set of perks from Year 4. If you want to see the old perks, here&amp;rsquo;s a still from Aztec&amp;rsquo;s review in 2019.
Cold Front Is Back &amp;amp; BETTER Than Ever! (Best Destiny 2 Primary?) - Ehroar
I believe it&amp;rsquo;s one of the best primaries in the game for PvE &amp;ndash; Ehroar, Dec.</description></item><item><title>[Compass Rose](https://www.light.gg/db/items/2591111628)</title><link>https://rslifka.github.io/sliflist/docs/world/compass_rose/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://rslifka.github.io/sliflist/docs/world/compass_rose/</guid><description>Compass Rose is a Precision Frame, Solar shotgun. It was available only during the Season 14 Solstice event.
🧲 Magnetic North (pvp) Classic &amp;ldquo;SnapDraw&amp;rdquo; shotgun roll. Compass Rose can roll with a few Range- increasing barrels in addition to just Full Choke and Rifled, so our odds of picking up these rolls is a bit better.
Collector&amp;rsquo;s Edition Roll
Barrels: Rifled Barrel, Full Choke Magazines: Accurized Rounds Perks 1: Quickdraw Perks 2: Snapshot Masterworks: Range MW Extended Perks (referred to with a &amp;lsquo;+&amp;rsquo; below)</description></item><item><title>[Dire Promise](https://www.light.gg/db/items/2742838701)</title><link>https://rslifka.github.io/sliflist/docs/world/dire_promise/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://rslifka.github.io/sliflist/docs/world/dire_promise/</guid><description>The Dire Promise is a 140 RPM Hand Cannon that was re-issued all the way back in Season 10 and much has changed. Sunsetting was introduced and then rolled back, 150 RPM HCs were collapsed into the 140 RPM frames and 110 RPMs were upgraded to 120 RPM, turning them into absolute PvP monsters. 140s are middle- of-the-pack but still pack a decent punch.
PvP Thoughts Once upon a time 120s rules the roost and 140s needed a bit of help.</description></item><item><title>[Eternity's Edge](https://www.light.gg/db/items/2782325301)</title><link>https://rslifka.github.io/sliflist/docs/world/eternitys_edge/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://rslifka.github.io/sliflist/docs/world/eternitys_edge/</guid><description>Eternity&amp;rsquo;s Edge is a Solar sword that was reissued as a Vortex Frame in Season 14.
⏳ Forever and a Day (pve) Surrounded and Vortex Frame swords were made for each other.
Collector&amp;rsquo;s Edition Roll
Barrels: Jagged Edge Magazines: Infinite Guard Perks 1: Relentless Strikes Perks 2: Surrounded Masterworks: Impact MW Extended Perks (referred to with a &amp;lsquo;+&amp;rsquo; below)
Barrels: Jagged Edge, Honed Edge, Tempered Edge Variant Chance 1 in ?</description></item><item><title>[First In, Last Out](https://www.light.gg/db/items/3616586446)</title><link>https://rslifka.github.io/sliflist/docs/world/first_in_last_out/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://rslifka.github.io/sliflist/docs/world/first_in_last_out/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;First In, Last Out&amp;rdquo; was released for the first time in Season 11 since its initial drop at the launch of Destiny 2 - Season 1! It&amp;rsquo;s the first time we&amp;rsquo;ve seen this with random rolls, so it does have a contemporary set of perks available (e.g. Demoiltionist and Vorpal). With the S14 shotgun nerf, and the mid-2020 precision damage PvE buff for Shotguns, (quoted below) this one should be at the top of your list.</description></item><item><title>[Gnawing Hunger](https://www.light.gg/db/items/821154603)</title><link>https://rslifka.github.io/sliflist/docs/world/gnawing_hunger/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://rslifka.github.io/sliflist/docs/world/gnawing_hunger/</guid><description>Gnawing Hunger is a 600 RPM &amp;ldquo;Adaptive Frame&amp;rdquo; Energy Auto Rifle first introduced in Season 6. It has been reissued in Season 11, meaning it will be capable of going up to the Season 14 power level cap. Adaptives were buffed Season 10 and slightly nerfed afterwards, yet remain strong.
PvP Thoughts For grins, check out ZkMushroom using the generally agreed-upon &amp;ldquo;God roll&amp;rdquo; roll with Tap the Trigger, Kill Clip and a Stability Masterwork.</description></item><item><title>[Hawkmoon](https://www.light.gg/db/items/3856705927)</title><link>https://rslifka.github.io/sliflist/docs/world/hawkmoon/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://rslifka.github.io/sliflist/docs/world/hawkmoon/</guid><description>Hawkmoon is a 140 RPM Exotic Hand Cannon, re-issued from Destiny 1 featuring random rolls! The base stats are terrific and it&amp;rsquo;s hard to argue that any single roll is &amp;ldquo;bad&amp;rdquo; per se, but there are certainly some rolls that are more desireable than others from a min/max&amp;rsquo;ers perspective.
PvP Thoughts If you haven&amp;rsquo;t already, complete the catalyst! Completing it grants you the masterwork:
&amp;ldquo;Increased magazine size. Grants increased handling, reload and weapon range based on the number of stacks of Paracausal Charge.</description></item></channel></rss>