<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Title - Sandbox - Weapons on</title><link>https://www.sliflist.com/sandbox/weapons/</link><description>Recent content in Title - Sandbox - Weapons on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:23 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.sliflist.com/sandbox/weapons/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Combat Bows</title><link>https://www.sliflist.com/sandbox/weapons/bows/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.sliflist.com/sandbox/weapons/bows/</guid><description>6/26/2020 - This section is nascent; needs a lot of work. Unfortunately not a ton of bow &amp;lsquo;science&amp;rsquo; out there, so this will be slow going.
Draw Time Is the one unique stat for bows. Every twenty points in Draw Time equates to 0.03 seconds, or one frame at 30fps. Lightweight bows are the fastest and have a floor of 540ms (i.e. any decrease beyond this will not take affect).</description></item><item><title>Fusion Rifles</title><link>https://www.sliflist.com/sandbox/weapons/fusion_rifles/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.sliflist.com/sandbox/weapons/fusion_rifles/</guid><description>2021/08/29: With the big S15 Fusion Rifle changes, much of this page needs reworking (ARGH). Left here for posterity.
Spicy Topics Charge Time Masterworks: Often seen as a instant dismantle, is it ever useful? When is Charge Time a useful Masterwork to bring up to 10? Is there some combination of Charge Time / Impact-modifying magazines that might affect that decision? High-Impact Reserves: There are issues with High-Impact Reserves with fusions when spawning in.</description></item><item><title>Hand Cannons</title><link>https://www.sliflist.com/sandbox/weapons/hand_cannons/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.sliflist.com/sandbox/weapons/hand_cannons/</guid><description>2021/08/29: Needs updating as the sandbox has changed with respect to Range on Hand Cannons
Effects of Range PART 1 : Range MEANS NOTHING on Hand Cannons - CoolGuy, 2019-10-28
Adding Range to a Hand Cannon has minimal gain. &amp;ldquo;You shouldn&amp;rsquo;t dismantle a great Hand Cannon roll because it isn&amp;rsquo;t max range.&amp;rdquo; When you add on Range to a Hand Cannon you get minimal gains: (35 Range = 25m falloff, 86 Range = 28m)</description></item><item><title>Shotguns</title><link>https://www.sliflist.com/sandbox/weapons/shotguns/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.sliflist.com/sandbox/weapons/shotguns/</guid><description>Season 15 Shotgun-related changes 7/6 3.2.1 - Too complex to summarize. Search for &amp;ldquo;Weapon Archetypes&amp;rdquo;. 8/21 TWAB - While sliding, players now incur the following weapon penalties: -20 Stability, +15% shotgun pellet spread, 1.5x flinch Rifled Barrel v. Full Choke Rifled Barrel vs Full Choke, Which is Better? - Fallout Plays, 2019-09-19
Tested both barrels on all four shotgun archetypes because there was a common misconception that barrels perform differently on different archetypes (they do not).</description></item><item><title>Swords</title><link>https://www.sliflist.com/sandbox/weapons/swords/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.sliflist.com/sandbox/weapons/swords/</guid><description>Fallout Plays put together a terrific in-depth analysis of everything Swords. If you know of any other content, please let me know!
Sword Frames Lightweight: Usable only by Hunters. There are two of these swords. Adaptive: Usable by all classes. While Warlocks do not have a specific type dedicate to them, they do have unique access to the Infinite Guard perk. Aggressive: Usable only by Titans. There are two of these as well.</description></item></channel></rss>