<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Iron Banner on</title><link>https://rslifka.github.io/sliflist/docs/ib/</link><description>Recent content in Iron Banner on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><atom:link href="https://rslifka.github.io/sliflist/docs/ib/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Bite of the Fox</title><link>https://rslifka.github.io/sliflist/docs/ib/bite_of_the_fox/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://rslifka.github.io/sliflist/docs/ib/bite_of_the_fox/</guid><description>For complete perks, see d2gunsmith.com, light.gg or destinytracker.com.
Bite of the Fox is a Kinetic-slot, Aggressive Frame sniper. It&amp;rsquo;s been in the Iron Banner loot pool since Season 4 and has been re-issued in Season 11. This means if you had a BOTF, it will hit the level cap this season, so you&amp;rsquo;ll want to get a new roll to take you past Season 11.
PvP Thoughts Aggressive Frame snipers are the only ones that can one-shot every super in the Crucible.</description></item><item><title>Crimil's Dagger</title><link>https://rslifka.github.io/sliflist/docs/ib/crimils_dagger/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://rslifka.github.io/sliflist/docs/ib/crimils_dagger/</guid><description>For complete perks, see d2gunsmith.com, light.gg or destinytracker.com.
Crimil&amp;rsquo;s is a 110 RPM Kinetic, Aggressive Frame Hand Cannon that has been re-issued in Season 11 with a higher power cap. It features the same perk pool its always had and since 110s haven&amp;rsquo;t been touched over the years dince Destiny 2&amp;rsquo;s launch, it&amp;rsquo;s going to be a pretty limited set of perks we&amp;rsquo;re interested in.
🧲 Magnetic Bullets (pvp) One of the rare weapons that can roll with both Moving Target and Opening Shot at the same time.</description></item><item><title>Fool's Remedy</title><link>https://rslifka.github.io/sliflist/docs/ib/fools_remedy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://rslifka.github.io/sliflist/docs/ib/fools_remedy/</guid><description>For complete perks, see d2gunsmith.com, light.gg or destinytracker.com.
Fool&amp;rsquo;s Remedy is &amp;ldquo;SUROS Rapid-Fire&amp;rdquo; (i.e. fully automatic) 450 RPM Sidearm that has been re-issued in Season 11&amp;rsquo;s Iron Banner. The Remedy is the only SUROS-RF sidearm in the game apart from Dead Man Walking.
If you&amp;rsquo;re going to chase a single weapon from Season 11 Iron Banner (thus far), the Fool&amp;rsquo;s Remedy is the one to go for. People are raving about it because of how it performs at base, its available perks, and that those perks now include the new Iron Banner specific perks: Iron Gaze and Iron Grip.</description></item><item><title>Orewing's Maul</title><link>https://rslifka.github.io/sliflist/docs/ib/orewings_maul/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://rslifka.github.io/sliflist/docs/ib/orewings_maul/</guid><description>For complete perks, see d2gunsmith.com, light.gg or destinytracker.com.
Orewing&amp;rsquo;s Maul is a Lightweight Frame, 90RPM Void Grenade Launcher. Orewing&amp;rsquo;s is almost identical to the Truthteller in every way, though it has a materially different (and less excellent) perk pool. Truthteller has more interesting combinations, but that doesn&amp;rsquo;t mean Orewing&amp;rsquo;s can&amp;rsquo;t put in work!
Like Truthteller, Orewing&amp;rsquo;s is part of the &amp;ldquo;Lightweight Frame&amp;rdquo; grenade launchers (breach-loaded, single shot). Lightweight grenade launchers all have a &amp;ldquo;remote detonation&amp;rdquo; ability where they detonate when you release the trigger (or you get a direct hit).</description></item><item><title>Talons of the Eagle</title><link>https://rslifka.github.io/sliflist/docs/ib/talons_of_the_eagle/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://rslifka.github.io/sliflist/docs/ib/talons_of_the_eagle/</guid><description>For complete perks, see d2gunsmith.com, light.gg or destinytracker.com.
Talons of the Eagle is a 150 RPM &amp;ldquo;High-Impact Frame&amp;rdquo; Kinetic Scout Rifle. It originally appeared wayyy back in Season 4 (aka Forsaken). It&amp;rsquo;s been recently re-issued in the first Season 11 Iron Banner. As part of this re-issue, the perk pool is unchanged, so we have years' worth of knowledge about how these work and years' worth of confusion as to why Scout Rifles can roll with Threat Detector and Hip-Fire Grip.</description></item><item><title>The Forward Path</title><link>https://rslifka.github.io/sliflist/docs/ib/the_forward_path/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://rslifka.github.io/sliflist/docs/ib/the_forward_path/</guid><description>For complete perks, see d2gunsmith.com, light.gg or destinytracker.com.
The Forward Path is a 600 RPM (Adaptive Frame) Kinetic Auto Rifle, brought back to us in Season 11 Iron Banner. It was in the first batch of IB weapons that featured the new Iron Gaze and Iron Grip perks.
PvP Thoughts The Forward Path, perhaps unsurprisingly given where it drops, is an absolute bear in PvP. 600 RPM ARs dominated the S11 meta and even though they were slightly reined in, they&amp;rsquo;re still phenomenal.</description></item><item><title>The Steady Hand</title><link>https://rslifka.github.io/sliflist/docs/ib/the_steady_hand/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://rslifka.github.io/sliflist/docs/ib/the_steady_hand/</guid><description>For complete perks, see d2gunsmith.com, light.gg or destinytracker.com.
The Steady Hand (TSH) is a 120 RPM &amp;ldquo;Aggressive Frame&amp;rdquo; Kinetic Hand Cannon, re-issued in Year 4 with random rolls. Prior to Season 12 in November 2020, Aggressive Frames were bumped from 110 RPM to 120 RPM as part of a large scale Hand Cannon rework. The general consensus thus far is that TSH is terrific.
PvP Thoughts The Steady Hand is probably the most consistent legendary 120 RPM aggressive hand cannon.</description></item></channel></rss>