<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Iron Banner on</title><link>https://rslifka.github.io/sliflist/docs/ib/</link><description>Recent content in Iron Banner on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><atom:link href="https://rslifka.github.io/sliflist/docs/ib/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Bite of the Fox</title><link>https://rslifka.github.io/sliflist/docs/ib/bite_of_the_fox/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://rslifka.github.io/sliflist/docs/ib/bite_of_the_fox/</guid><description>Bite of the Fox is a Kinetic-slot, Aggressive Frame sniper. It&amp;rsquo;s been in the Iron Banner loot pool since Season 4 and has been re-issued in Season 11. This means if you had a BOTF, it will hit the level cap this season, so you&amp;rsquo;ll want to get a new roll to take you past Season 11.
🤞 Snappy Opener (pvp) This series of rolls is based around Snapshot and Accuracy-increasing final-column perks.</description></item><item><title>Crimil's Dagger</title><link>https://rslifka.github.io/sliflist/docs/ib/crimil_s_dagger/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://rslifka.github.io/sliflist/docs/ib/crimil_s_dagger/</guid><description>Crimil&amp;rsquo;s is a 110 RPM Kinetic, Aggressive Frame Hand Cannon that has been re-issued in Season 11 with a higher power cap. It features the same perk pool its always had and since 110s haven&amp;rsquo;t been touched over the years dince Destiny 2&amp;rsquo;s launch, it&amp;rsquo;s going to be a pretty limited set of perks we&amp;rsquo;re interested in.
🧲 Magnetic Bullets (pvp) One of the rare weapons that can roll with both Moving Target and Opening Shot at the same time.</description></item><item><title>Fool's Remedy</title><link>https://rslifka.github.io/sliflist/docs/ib/fool_s_remedy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://rslifka.github.io/sliflist/docs/ib/fool_s_remedy/</guid><description>Fool&amp;rsquo;s Remedy is &amp;ldquo;SUROS Rapid-Fire&amp;rdquo; (i.e. fully automatic) 450 RPM Sidearm that has been re-issued in Season 11&amp;rsquo;s Iron Banner. The Remedy is the only SUROS-RF sidearm in the game apart from Dead Man Walking whose power cap is the current Season (11).
👓 In my Sights (pvp) Working backwards from Iron Gaze (+20 AA), we&amp;rsquo;re going for as much Stability as we can. We&amp;rsquo;d end choosing the rest of the roll similarly if we landed Kill Clip or Eye of the Storm in the final slot, so we&amp;rsquo;ll combine these rolls.</description></item><item><title>Orewing's Maul</title><link>https://rslifka.github.io/sliflist/docs/ib/orewing_s_maul/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://rslifka.github.io/sliflist/docs/ib/orewing_s_maul/</guid><description>Orewing&amp;rsquo;s is almost identical to the Truthteller in every way, save for a much less excellent perk pool. Truthteller has more interesting combinations, but if you&amp;rsquo;re swimming in GL&amp;rsquo;s from Iron Banner and really want to keep one, read on.
Destiny Fun Police (aka DFP) first popularized these back in Year 1 of Destiny 2 when he used the Fighting Lion to great affect.
Like Truthteller, Orewing&amp;rsquo;s is part of the &amp;ldquo;Lightweight Frame&amp;rdquo; grenade launchers (breach-loaded, single shot).</description></item><item><title>Swarm of the Raven</title><link>https://rslifka.github.io/sliflist/docs/ib/swarm_of_the_raven/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://rslifka.github.io/sliflist/docs/ib/swarm_of_the_raven/</guid><description>For a moment in time, Swarm of the Raven was a legit DPS option. It&amp;rsquo;s a Void Grenade Launcher and the buff from Tractor Cannon made it a beast. It&amp;rsquo;s not super hot anymore, but why not secure yourself a good one just in case? Chances are without even trying you&amp;rsquo;re going to get a pretty decent roll. Enjoy!
🦅 Dive Bomb (pve) More impact damage and ammo reserves, along with bumped Velocity.</description></item><item><title>Talons of the Eagle</title><link>https://rslifka.github.io/sliflist/docs/ib/talons_of_the_eagle/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://rslifka.github.io/sliflist/docs/ib/talons_of_the_eagle/</guid><description>Talons of the Eagle is a 150 RPM &amp;ldquo;High-Impact Frame&amp;rdquo; Kinetic Scout Rifle. It originally appeared wayyy back in Season 4 (aka Forsaken). It&amp;rsquo;s been recently re-issued in the first Season 11 Iron Banner. As part of this re-issue, the perk pool is unchanged, so we have years' worth of knowledge about how these work and years' worth of confusion as to why Scout Rifles can roll with Threat Detector and Hip-Fire Grip.</description></item><item><title>The Forward Path</title><link>https://rslifka.github.io/sliflist/docs/ib/the_forward_path/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://rslifka.github.io/sliflist/docs/ib/the_forward_path/</guid><description>The Forward Path is a 600 RPM (Adaptive Frame) Kinetic Auto Rifle, brought back to us in Season 11 Iron Banner. It was in the first batch of IB weapons that featured the new Iron Gaze and Iron Grip perks.
🏃‍♂️ Chasing Stability (pvp) Tap the Trigger starts you off stable and Dynamic Sway Reduction keeps you stable. Iron Grip is a crazy boost to Stability.
Collector&amp;rsquo;s Edition Perks
Barrels: Red Dot Micro, Red Dot 2 MOA Magazines: Steady Rounds Perks 1: Dynamic Sway Reduction Perks 2: Tap the Trigger, Iron Grip Masterworks: Stability MW Extended Perks (referred to with a &amp;lsquo;+&amp;rsquo; below)</description></item><item><title>The Steady Hand</title><link>https://rslifka.github.io/sliflist/docs/ib/the_steady_hand/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://rslifka.github.io/sliflist/docs/ib/the_steady_hand/</guid><description>The Steady Hand (TSH) is a 120 RPM &amp;ldquo;Aggressive Frame&amp;rdquo; Kinetic Hand Cannon, re-issued in Year 4 with random rolls. Prior to Season 12 in November 2020, Aggressive Frames were bumped from 110 RPM to 120 RPM as part of a large scale Hand Cannon rework. The general consensus thus far is that TSH is terrific.
🔒 Locked On (pvp) Moving Target and Iron Gaze are going to bump Target Acquisition immensely.</description></item></channel></rss>