<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Raid - Vault of Glass on</title><link>https://www.sliflist.com/docs/vog/</link><description>Recent content in Raid - Vault of Glass on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><atom:link href="https://www.sliflist.com/docs/vog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Corrective Measure</title><link>https://www.sliflist.com/docs/vog/corrective_measure/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.sliflist.com/docs/vog/corrective_measure/</guid><description>For complete perks, see d2gunsmith.com, light.gg or destinytracker.com.
The Corrective Measure is a 450 RPM Adaptive Frame Machine Gun that drops in the Vault of Glass (Confluxes, Templar and Atheon).
That is the reason why Corrective Measure is one of my favorite Machine Guns of all time, because it bridges the gap of two of the best builds I like to use. &amp;hellip; The Corrective Measure is the perfect Machine Gun and I don&amp;rsquo;t think it will ever be surpassed - Ehroar</description></item><item><title>Fatebringer</title><link>https://www.sliflist.com/docs/vog/fatebringer/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.sliflist.com/docs/vog/fatebringer/</guid><description>For complete perks, see d2gunsmith.com, light.gg or destinytracker.com.
Fatebringer is a 140 RPM hand cannon, back in a reprised version from the Vault of Glass. In D2, it&amp;rsquo;s a kinetic (in D1 it was Arc). It drops in the Vault of Glass from Templar or Gatekeeper encounters. Once acquired, it will also drop from either of the two secret chests and can be acquired from the post-Atheon chest for Spoils of Conquest x 20.</description></item><item><title>Fatebringer (Timelost)</title><link>https://www.sliflist.com/docs/vog/fatebringer_timelost/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.sliflist.com/docs/vog/fatebringer_timelost/</guid><description>For complete perks, see d2gunsmith.com, light.gg or destinytracker.com.
This is the &amp;ldquo;Timelost&amp;rdquo; (or &amp;ldquo;Adept&amp;rdquo;) version of this weapon, which drops only by completing the Conflux encounter Challenge in Vault of Glass on Master mode. The rolls here are the same as the normal version except with a higher drop chance because the Timelost version comes with double perks in the final two columns. The Adept version comes with static rolls in column 3 (Explosive Payload) and in column 4 (Firefly), both solid perks.</description></item><item><title>Hezen Vengeance</title><link>https://www.sliflist.com/docs/vog/hezen_vengeance/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.sliflist.com/docs/vog/hezen_vengeance/</guid><description>For complete perks, see d2gunsmith.com, light.gg or destinytracker.com.
Hezen Vengeance is a 25 RPM Aggressive Frame Rocket Launcher that drops in the Vault of Glass from the Gatekeeper or Atheon encounters. It&amp;rsquo;s the only Rocket Launcher in the game currently that can roll with Overflow which makes it a DPS monster.
PvE Thoughts A few highlights from Ehroar&amp;rsquo;s review combined with highlights from Rustopholis' video on Rocket Launcher perks in general.</description></item><item><title>Vision of Confluence</title><link>https://www.sliflist.com/docs/vog/vision_of_confluence/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.sliflist.com/docs/vog/vision_of_confluence/</guid><description>For complete perks, see d2gunsmith.com, light.gg or destinytracker.com.
Vision of Confluence is a 180 RPM Precision Frame Scout Rifle. It&amp;rsquo;s one of three 180 RPMs currently available. It drops in the Vault of Glass from the first three encounters: Conflux, Oracles and the Templar. Once acquired, it will also drop from either of the two secret chests and can be acquired from the post-Atheon chest for Spoils of Conquest x 20.</description></item><item><title>Vision of Confluence (Timelost)</title><link>https://www.sliflist.com/docs/vog/vision_of_confluence_timelost/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.sliflist.com/docs/vog/vision_of_confluence_timelost/</guid><description>For complete perks, see d2gunsmith.com, light.gg or destinytracker.com.
This is the &amp;ldquo;Timelost&amp;rdquo; (or &amp;ldquo;Adept&amp;rdquo;) version of this weapon, which drops only by completing the Conflux encounter Challenge in Vault of Glass on Master mode.
The rolls here are the same as the normal version except with a higher drop chance because the Timelost version comes with double perks in the final two columns.
⏱ Partners in Time (pvp) Tunnel Vision and Kill Clip both proc on reload - they were made for each other!</description></item></channel></rss>