<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>S11 - Season of the Arrivals on</title><link>https://rslifka.github.io/sliflist/docs/11/</link><description>Recent content in S11 - Season of the Arrivals on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><atom:link href="https://rslifka.github.io/sliflist/docs/11/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>[Cold Denial](https://www.light.gg/db/items/1216130969)</title><link>https://rslifka.github.io/sliflist/docs/11/cold_denial/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://rslifka.github.io/sliflist/docs/11/cold_denial/</guid><description>Cold Denial is a 340 RPM &amp;ldquo;High-Impact Frame&amp;rdquo; Kinetic Pulse Rifle introduced in Season 11. See how it compares to the existing High-Impacts. The major difference might seem like a minor one, but check out the Zoom:14 compared to the others with Zoom:18. The lower zoom means you&amp;rsquo;ve got a wider FOV while zoomed in, and that small(er) thumbstick movements don&amp;rsquo;t kick your reticle as much. It makes way more of a difference than it might seem like on paper.</description></item><item><title>[Falling Guillotine](https://www.light.gg/db/items/614426548)</title><link>https://rslifka.github.io/sliflist/docs/11/falling_guillotine/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://rslifka.github.io/sliflist/docs/11/falling_guillotine/</guid><description>Dark Drinker 2.0 is&amp;hellip; sorry I mean Falling Guillotine&amp;hellip; is a new &amp;ldquo;Vortex Frame&amp;rdquo; sword in S11. It does a ridiculous - amount - of - damage and is also just weird.
If you&amp;rsquo;ve ever been confused about sword perks, there is a terrific post I regularly refer to over on /r/DtG: Everything You Need to Know About Swords in Season of the Worthy
👑 Reign&amp;rsquo;s End (pve) Use Whirlwind to help build up damage before you shoot off a Heavy Attack.</description></item><item><title>[False Promises](https://www.light.gg/db/items/3143732432)</title><link>https://rslifka.github.io/sliflist/docs/11/false_promises/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://rslifka.github.io/sliflist/docs/11/false_promises/</guid><description>False Promises is a 360 RPM Kinetic Auto Rifle introduced in Season 11. The High-Impacts are notable by their extremely long Range and extremely poor Stability and False Promises is no exception. On console, False Promises is pretty tough to control. Even with vertical Recoil, there&amp;rsquo;s still a lot of bounce in the reticle because the Stability is so low.
PvP Thoughts I&amp;rsquo;m recommending, nay requiring Dynamic Sway Reduction for any False Promises roll I&amp;rsquo;d consider using in PvP, because of its marked affect on Stability and Accuracy.</description></item><item><title>[Temptation's Hook](https://www.light.gg/db/items/35794111)</title><link>https://rslifka.github.io/sliflist/docs/11/temptations_hook/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://rslifka.github.io/sliflist/docs/11/temptations_hook/</guid><description>Temptation&amp;rsquo;s Hook is the first &amp;ldquo;Caster Frame&amp;rdquo; sword to appear in the game. It&amp;rsquo;s Heavy Attack swipe is replaced with a projectile that (at full sword energy) grinds away when it hits an enemy. You can make great use of these against enemies where peeking is helpful, for example Shriekers or keeping a beefy enemy from regenerating its shield. Courtesy of this analysis, Jagged Edge is the clear choice for the first column, and since we want to throw as many projectiles as we can, it&amp;rsquo;s Swordmaster's Guard for the second column.</description></item><item><title>[Whispering Slab](https://www.light.gg/db/items/211938782)</title><link>https://rslifka.github.io/sliflist/docs/11/whispering_slab/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://rslifka.github.io/sliflist/docs/11/whispering_slab/</guid><description>🌟💥🎉 BOW HYPE TIME 🌟💥🎉 BOW HYPE TIME 🌟💥🎉 BOW HYPE TIME 🌟💥🎉
PvP Thoughts Remember when we all thought Wish-Ender would break the Crucible because you could see through walls? That&amp;rsquo;s the last time I thought bows might break the sandbox, or really even ever thought about using bows in PvP at all. Did you even know you can see through walls with Wish-Ender? I digress&amp;hellip;
Many months ago, I saved a post by /u/TheGuiltySpark117 in the off chance I ever wanted to give bows a real shot in PvP.</description></item></channel></rss>