<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Title - Welcome - Index on</title><link>https://www.sliflist.com/docs/welcome/</link><description>Recent content in Title - Welcome - Index on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:45 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.sliflist.com/docs/welcome/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Introduction</title><link>https://www.sliflist.com/docs/welcome/introduction/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.sliflist.com/docs/welcome/introduction/</guid><description>Welcome to the Sliflist! The homepage is a good place to start.
Getting Around 👆 Search Bar: The quickest way to find what you&amp;rsquo;re looking for. 👈 Roll Catalog: Organized by where or when the weapon drops. Bungie is always expanding the world loot pool, and to ease confusion, that&amp;rsquo;s been extracted into a separate category. Seasons contain only the season-specific set of weapons.</description></item><item><title>Contributing</title><link>https://www.sliflist.com/docs/welcome/contributing/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.sliflist.com/docs/welcome/contributing/</guid><description>There are two ways to contribute to the Sliflist.
1 - Suggest / Tweak Rolls Roll philosophy and format is discussed over in &amp;ldquo;What&amp;rsquo;s in a Roll?&amp;quot;.
2 - Improve the Sliflist Itself To see about contributing to the codebase that creates the wishlist and generates this site, head over to @rslifka/sliflist.</description></item><item><title>What's in a Roll?</title><link>https://www.sliflist.com/docs/welcome/roll_format/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.sliflist.com/docs/welcome/roll_format/</guid><description>With so many weapons and potential rolls, one main goal of the Sliflist is to make submitting rolls as easy as possible to reduce the barrier to populating the Sliflist. In order to do that, we first need to explain the roll format and how a roll turns into DIM wishlist entries.
Sliflist Thesis Over the past two years, we&amp;rsquo;ve noticed that many rolls fall into the same pattern:
The perfect (aka &amp;ldquo;god&amp;rdquo;) roll, getting exactly what perks you want in every column, including the masterwork.</description></item><item><title>Missing Rolls</title><link>https://www.sliflist.com/docs/welcome/missing_rolls/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.sliflist.com/docs/welcome/missing_rolls/</guid><description>If you&amp;rsquo;re interested in contributing, this is a great place to get started! It&amp;rsquo;s a list of currently available weapons that are not presently in the Sliflist.
This list is still a work in progress. There&amp;rsquo;s a lot of weapons in Destiny!
Weapon Drops From Ascendancy S15 Canis Major S15 Chrysura Melo S15 Fractethyst S15 Iota Draconis S15 Wolftone Draw S15 Darkest Before Prophecy Judgment Prophecy A Sudden Death Prophecy A Swift Verdict Prophecy The Last Breath Prophecy The Long Walk Prophecy Peacebond Iron Banner Forge&amp;rsquo;s Pledge Iron Banner Bequest Deep Stone Crypt Commemoration Deep Stone Crypt Succession Deep Stone Crypt Trustee Deep Stone Crypt Praedyth&amp;rsquo;s Revenge Vault of Glass Praedyth&amp;rsquo;s Revenge (Timelost) Vault of Glass Fatebringer Vault of Glass Fatebringer (Timelost) Vault of Glass The Comedian Grandmaster Nightfalls The Comedian (Adept) Grandmaster Nightfalls The Hothead Grandmaster Nightfalls The Hothead (Adept) Grandmaster Nightfalls Reed&amp;rsquo;s Regret Trials of Osiris Reed&amp;rsquo;s Regret (Adept) Trials of Osiris Annual Skate World Contingency Plan World Legal Action II World Punching Out World Scathelocke World Servant Leader World Shepherd&amp;rsquo;s Watch World Sorrow&amp;rsquo;s Verse World</description></item></channel></rss>