<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>S13 - Season of the Chosen on</title><link>https://www.sliflist.com/docs/13/</link><description>Recent content in S13 - Season of the Chosen on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><atom:link href="https://www.sliflist.com/docs/13/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Code Duello</title><link>https://www.sliflist.com/docs/13/code_duello/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.sliflist.com/docs/13/code_duello/</guid><description>For complete perks, see d2gunsmith.com, light.gg or destinytracker.com.
Code Duello is the Season 13 Rocket Launcher. You can pick it up from chests in the Battlegrounds playlists and Umbral Engrams. It features a handful of the new S13 perks including Impulse Amplifier, Frenzy and Lasting Impression. Ehroar put together a solid video review comparing them and offering some suggestions for interesting rolls. You&amp;rsquo;re going to be drowning in these by the end of Season 13 and with the new damage perks, these are worth picking up!</description></item><item><title>Extraordinary Rendition</title><link>https://www.sliflist.com/docs/13/extraordinary_rendition/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.sliflist.com/docs/13/extraordinary_rendition/</guid><description>For complete perks, see d2gunsmith.com, light.gg or destinytracker.com.
Extraordinary Rendition is a 750 RPM Kinetic Submachine Gun; part of the S13 weapon set. Both perks and stats are virtually identical to the Cold Front, available only during the 2020 Dawning, so we&amp;rsquo;ll be able to rely on the work we did there for these rolls 🎉🎉🎉 Ehroar covers the Extraordinary Rendition in depth.
The cornerstone of both PvE and PvP are Surplus.</description></item><item><title>Imperial Needle</title><link>https://www.sliflist.com/docs/13/imperial_needle/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.sliflist.com/docs/13/imperial_needle/</guid><description>For complete perks, see d2gunsmith.com, light.gg or destinytracker.com.
The Needle is a Lightweight Frame, Void Bow, part of the S13 family of seasonal weapons. It can roll with many of the new perks including Frenzy and Impulse Amplifier. It&amp;rsquo;s otherwise quite similar to the Whispering Slab in terms of base stats.
As per usual, I suggest checking out these amazing posts:
A Bow Guide - /u/kfairns An In-Depth Guide to Using a Bow in Competitive PvP (Console or PC) - /u/TheGuiltySpark117 The new perks don&amp;rsquo;t change the suggested PvP rolls from Whispering Slab, so these rolls will be straight reproductions from what we previously covered when S11 dropped.</description></item><item><title>Threaded Needle</title><link>https://www.sliflist.com/docs/13/threaded_needle/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.sliflist.com/docs/13/threaded_needle/</guid><description>For complete perks, see d2gunsmith.com, light.gg or destinytracker.com.
Threaded Needle is a void Linear Fusion rifle available since season 13, which was only of interest to people who want to hit crits, in exchange for middling boss damage, and no particular add-clear value. Then the Particle Deconstruction mod arrived in season 15, and made it one of the best DPS options in the game. This is why your vault is always full.</description></item></channel></rss>