<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>S10 - Season of the Worthy on</title><link>https://www.sliflist.com/docs/10/</link><description>Recent content in S10 - Season of the Worthy on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><atom:link href="https://www.sliflist.com/docs/10/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Seventh Seraph Carbine</title><link>https://www.sliflist.com/docs/10/seventh_seraph_carbine/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.sliflist.com/docs/10/seventh_seraph_carbine/</guid><description>For complete perks, see d2gunsmith.com, light.gg or destinytracker.com.
The Seventh Seraph Carbine (SSC) is a 450 RPM Precision Frame Kinetic Auto Rifle. Let&amp;rsquo;s start with a quick comparison to randomly-rolled 450s, over on light.gg. In general the 450s are fairly the same stat-wise, with a material deviation in Aim Assist for the SSC; easily addressable with an Aim Assist mod.
PvP Thoughts I personally love ARs, so I played with a zero-Recoil, high Stability roll for several Iron Banner games, with both Targeting and Unflinching mods equippted.</description></item><item><title>Seventh Seraph CQC-12</title><link>https://www.sliflist.com/docs/10/seventh_seraph_cqc_12/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.sliflist.com/docs/10/seventh_seraph_cqc_12/</guid><description>For complete perks, see d2gunsmith.com, light.gg or destinytracker.com.
The CQC-12 is an 80 RPM &amp;ldquo;Lightweight Frame&amp;rdquo; shotgun in the energy slot. There are only four perks in the final two columns meaning you&amp;rsquo;re more likely to get a decent roll more quickly.
See how it compares to other randomly-rolled Lightweights over on light.gg. Statistically, they&amp;rsquo;re all quite similar and like most shotguns, otherwise identical in barrels and magazines.
Most important, the CQC-12 looks and sounds amazing, and that&amp;rsquo;s like 80% of the reason to use a weapon anyway, right?</description></item><item><title>Seventh Seraph Officer Revolver</title><link>https://www.sliflist.com/docs/10/seventh_seraph_officer_revolver/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.sliflist.com/docs/10/seventh_seraph_officer_revolver/</guid><description>For complete perks, see d2gunsmith.com, light.gg or destinytracker.com.
The Officer Revolver is a 180 RPM Kinetic Hand Cannon that first appeared in Season 10. By today&amp;rsquo;s standards, it&amp;rsquo;s perk pool feels a bit dated however it maintains relevancy for two key reasons: it&amp;rsquo;s a Seraph weapon so it generates Warmind Cells and it&amp;rsquo;s one of the rare weapons that drops with Timed Payload, useful in both PvP and PvE.
PvP Thoughts Meta-wise, 180s are not the play however that doesn&amp;rsquo;t mean you can&amp;rsquo;t make magic with them in PvP.</description></item><item><title>Seventh Seraph SAW</title><link>https://www.sliflist.com/docs/10/seventh_seraph_saw/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.sliflist.com/docs/10/seventh_seraph_saw/</guid><description>For complete perks, see d2gunsmith.com, light.gg or destinytracker.com.
The Seventh Seraph SAW is a 360 RPM, High-Impact Frame, Arc Machine Gun that first appeared in Season 10. MGs haven&amp;rsquo;t been bananas in PvE for some time (save for the Xenopage), and so in the final TWAB of Season 14 Bungie announced that they&amp;rsquo;re increasing PvE damage of Machine Guns by 25%.
In lieu of being able to find anyone covering the SAW, I looked for coverage of other 360 RPM Machine Guns.</description></item><item><title>Seventh Seraph SI-2</title><link>https://www.sliflist.com/docs/10/seventh_seraph_si_2/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.sliflist.com/docs/10/seventh_seraph_si_2/</guid><description>For complete perks, see d2gunsmith.com, light.gg or destinytracker.com.
The SI-2 is a 360 RPM Lightweight Frame Arc Sidearm, initially appearing during Season 10.
PvP Thoughts TrueVanguard, who absolutely loves the Anonymous Autumn (with over 14,000 kills) depicts the SI-2 as situational, relying primarily on Vorpal to justify using it. Check out his thoughts. If you are going to consider the SI-2 for PvP, a few things to keep in mind. The recoil direction is 95, so no need to worry about straightening it out.</description></item><item><title>Seventh Seraph VY-7</title><link>https://www.sliflist.com/docs/10/seventh_seraph_vy_7/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.sliflist.com/docs/10/seventh_seraph_vy_7/</guid><description>For complete perks, see d2gunsmith.com, light.gg or destinytracker.com.
The Seventh Seraph VY-7 is a 600 RPM Precision Frame Arc SMG, initially made available during Season 10 (remember the bunkers?). It continues to drop as part of the world loot pool.
PvP Thoughts Remember this world?
Antiope-D&amp;rsquo;s FINAL FORM! (God Roll) - Destiny Fun Police The Perfect Antiope-D does exist! - CammyCakes Antiope-D and Sniping = New Meta ? - ZkMushroom The VY-7 is basically an Energy-slot Antiope-D as the basic stat variances are immaterial in practice.</description></item></channel></rss>