<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>S14 - Season of the Splicer on</title><link>https://rslifka.github.io/sliflist/docs/14/</link><description>Recent content in S14 - Season of the Splicer on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><atom:link href="https://rslifka.github.io/sliflist/docs/14/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Chroma Rush</title><link>https://rslifka.github.io/sliflist/docs/14/chroma_rush/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://rslifka.github.io/sliflist/docs/14/chroma_rush/</guid><description>Chroma Rush is one of the many beautiful new weapons available in S14. It&amp;rsquo;s a 720 RPM Rapid-Fire Frame Auto Rifle; the only available in the game apart from Arctic Haze. See how they compare over on light.gg. Artic Haze suffered from a punishing base recoil and a lack of stability and damage-dealing perks whereas Chroma has both of those in spades.
🔥 Catching Fire (pvp) With Heating Up and Kill Clip going, Chroma Rush feels like a longer-range Recluse.</description></item><item><title>Farewell</title><link>https://rslifka.github.io/sliflist/docs/14/farewell/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://rslifka.github.io/sliflist/docs/14/farewell/</guid><description>Farewell is a Lightweight frame, 360 RPM Sidearm introduced in S14. It&amp;rsquo;s the only Kinetic Lightweight available in the game, and the only other sidearm of that type entirely.
🛫 exit(0) (pvp) Pairing together perks that proc after kills/reloads to set us up for streaks. We&amp;rsquo;ll take any combo of top-tier Stability- or Range- enhancing perks as follow-ups.
Collector&amp;rsquo;s Edition Roll
Barrels: Chambered Compensator, Hammer-Forged Rifling Magazines: Steady Rounds, Accurized Rounds Perks 1: Tunnel Vision, Heating Up Perks 2: Multikill Clip Masterworks: Stability MW, Range MW Extended Perks (referred to with a &amp;lsquo;+&amp;rsquo; below)</description></item><item><title>Gridskipper</title><link>https://rslifka.github.io/sliflist/docs/14/gridskipper/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://rslifka.github.io/sliflist/docs/14/gridskipper/</guid><description>Gridskipper is a 540RPM Rapid-Fire Pulse Rifle introduced in Season 14. It&amp;rsquo;s the only 540 RPM Energy Pulse Rifle available at the moment and drops with all of the new seasonal perks. Definitely pick this up if you frequent the Crucible.
🥵 Heat Dome (pvp) The two new third-column perks Heating Up and Tunnel Vision are brilliant on the Gridskipper. I&amp;rsquo;m partial to Heating Up but people love them both. The roll wouldn&amp;rsquo;t otherwise be different so I&amp;rsquo;m combining them here.</description></item><item><title>Ignition Code</title><link>https://rslifka.github.io/sliflist/docs/14/ignition_code/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://rslifka.github.io/sliflist/docs/14/ignition_code/</guid><description>The most important weapon to get this season that will be relevant in the PvE meta for some time&amp;quot; - Ehroar
This thing is horrifying. It&amp;rsquo;s going to remind you of The Mountaintop It&amp;rsquo;s like a full-auto GL! - Frostbolt
Well, I&amp;rsquo;m not sure the world of players will get as much utility out of this in PvP as Frostbolt does, but you will definitely make magic with it inside of PvE.</description></item><item><title>Shattered Cipher</title><link>https://rslifka.github.io/sliflist/docs/14/shattered_cipher/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://rslifka.github.io/sliflist/docs/14/shattered_cipher/</guid><description>The Cipher is a 900 RPM Machine Gun that arrived in Season 14. There are many excellent MGs in the pool right now, so this one has some tough competition. The Cipher has arguably has the least interesting set of perks to choose among.
In the April 29, 2021 TWAB Bungie refers to MGs (reformatted):
Machine Guns are used for ammo-efficient add clear and secondary single target sustained damage. We expect to adjust Machine Guns in a future Season, they&amp;rsquo;re not currently hitting this target.</description></item><item><title>Sojourner's Tale</title><link>https://rslifka.github.io/sliflist/docs/14/sojourners_tale/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://rslifka.github.io/sliflist/docs/14/sojourners_tale/</guid><description>Sojourner&amp;rsquo;s Tale is a Legendary Slug Shotgun in the Energy slot, introduced in S14.
📖 The Tale of Coolguy (pvp) Coolguy has a terrific video breakdown of Soujourner&amp;rsquo;s Tale. It&amp;rsquo;s the only weapon in the game that can roll with this combo of Tunnel Vision and Killing Wind, which both proc on reload. What was new to me was that the benefits proc as soon as a single shell has been reloaded.</description></item></channel></rss>