<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>S15 - Season of the Lost on</title><link>https://www.sliflist.com/docs/15/</link><description>Recent content in S15 - Season of the Lost on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><atom:link href="https://www.sliflist.com/docs/15/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Fractethyst</title><link>https://www.sliflist.com/docs/15/fractethyst/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.sliflist.com/docs/15/fractethyst/</guid><description>For complete perks, see d2gunsmith.com, light.gg or destinytracker.com.
Fractethyst is a Precision Frame (65 RPM) Stasis Shotgun, introduced in Season 15. The best roundup I&amp;rsquo;ve seen is courtesy of Castle Content, and much of what you&amp;rsquo;ll see here is recapped from his review.
PvP Thoughts Finally a replacement for the fallen king of Destiny Shotguns Dust Rock Blues! Fractethyst will round out your Kinetic slot shotgun suite and will do it in style, with some super interesting new perks.</description></item><item><title>Iota Draconis</title><link>https://www.sliflist.com/docs/15/iota_draconis/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.sliflist.com/docs/15/iota_draconis/</guid><description>For complete perks, see d2gunsmith.com, light.gg or destinytracker.com.
With season 15&amp;rsquo;s changes to High-Impact Frame pulse rifles, you now have to charge for a full second to shoot five bolts, four of which still have to land in PVP to turn another player into pretty sparkles. This PVP roll aims to bring that down to three bolts.
PvP Thoughts &amp;hellip;
PvE Thoughts &amp;hellip;
🔩 Mercules' Three-Bolt Special (pvp) Reaching for a three-bolt kill in PVP.</description></item><item><title>Vulpecula</title><link>https://www.sliflist.com/docs/15/vulpecula/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.sliflist.com/docs/15/vulpecula/</guid><description>For complete perks, see d2gunsmith.com, light.gg or destinytracker.com.
Vulpecula is a 180 RPM Kinetic Stasis Hand Cannon, introduced in Season of the Lost (S15). If you&amp;rsquo;re confused and barely able to pronounce the names of the Season 15 weapons, so am I! Fortunately, the Sliflist is here to help. From Wikipedia:
Vulpecula /vʌlˈpɛkjʊlə/ is a faint constellation in the northern sky. Its name is Latin for &amp;ldquo;little fox&amp;rdquo;, although it is commonly known simply as the fox.</description></item></channel></rss>